<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Alex Wermer-Colan</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Alex Wermer-Colan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hawc2.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/about/</guid><description>About Me I am a writer, editor, translator, and teacher.
Research Interest I am interested in the intersection of politics, aesthetics, and technology. In my writing and my advocacy I explore ways of reverse engineering infrastructure and media at a time of cultural decline.
Publications The New Wave of Digital Collections, The American Philosophical Society Immersive Pedagogy, The Journal of Interactive Technology and Pedagogy</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Contact Professional Email Social Github Twitter</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/cv/</guid><description>CV ACADEMIC APPOINTMENTS Digital Scholarship Coordinator (2021-Present) Temple University, Charles Library, Scholars Studio Council of Library Information Resources and Digital Humanities Postdoctoral Fellowship (2017-2020) Temple University, Samuel Paley Library, Digital Scholarship Center
EDUCATION Ph.D., English, The Graduate Center, City University of New York (2017) Certificate: Critical Theory M.A., Humanities, University of Chicago (2009) B.A., Liberal Arts, Vassar College (2007)
RESEARCH AND TEACHING INTERESTS Twentieth-Century American, British, and French Literature; Critical Theory; Post-Colonialism; Gender and Sexuality; Archival Studies; Cinema and Media Studies; Digital Humanities; Cultural Analytics; Natural Language Processing; Immersive Technologies (XR/AR/VR), Dramaturgy</description></item></channel></rss>