<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Alex Wermer-Colan</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Alex Wermer-Colan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hawc2.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coding</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/coding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/coding/</guid><description>Various scripts, computing projects, Github resources, etc.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Hello
Email
Github
Twitter</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/cv/</guid><description>CV ACADEMIC APPOINTMENTS Digital Scholarship Coordinator (2021-Present) Temple University, Charles Library, Scholars Studio
Council of Library Information Resources and Digital Humanities Postdoctoral Fellowship (2017-2020) Temple University, Samuel Paley Library, Digital Scholarship Center
EDUCATION Ph.D., English, The Graduate Center, City University of New York (2017) Certificate: Critical Theory
M.A., Humanities, University of Chicago (2009) B.A., Liberal Arts, Vassar College (2007)
LANGUAGES French: Writing (proficient), Reading (fluent), speaking (proficient) Spanish: Writing (proficient), Reading (proficient), speaking (conversational)</description></item><item><title>Dramaturgy</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/dramaturgy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/dramaturgy/</guid><description>Theater Decoder Performances
ART RESIDENCIES Pioneer Works Arts Residency, Pioneer Works, Brooklyn, NY (2019)
Watermill Arts Residency, Watermill Center, Long Island, NY (2019)
Experimental Theater Arts Residency, Collapsible Hole, New York, NY (2019)
Mabou Mines Arts Residency, Mabou Mines, New York, NY (2018)
The Watershed Lab Residency, Mount Tremper Arts, Mount Tremper, NY (2017)
Music Travel Agency adaptations
Experiments in Opera
Script-writing Inaccessible PCW Animation</description></item><item><title>Pedagogy</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/pedagogy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/pedagogy/</guid><description>TEACHING POSITIONS Adjunct Assistant Professor, Guttman Community College, CUNY (2017)
“Composition I” (2 sections): Required, writing-intensive
Graduate Teaching Fellowship (sole instructor), Hunter College, CUNY (2011-2017)
“Imperial Decadence” (2 sections): Writing intensive seminar for English majors
“Introduction to Writing about Literature” (15 sections): Required, writing-intensive
“Introduction to Literary Studies: Colonial to Post-Colonial Lit” (2 sections): Required for English majors
“Introduction to Literary Studies: Post-WWII American Literature” (1 section): Required for English majors</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/projects/</guid><description>DIGITAL PROJECTS Philly Community Wireless, Admin Lead (2020-2021)
Inaccessible, Game Design (2020)
Visionary Futures Collective (2020-2021)
SF Nexus: Digitizing and Curating Speculative Fiction, Project Director (2017-Present)
The Virtual Blockson: A Virtual Recreation of the Charles L. Blockson Afro-American Collection for Primary Source Literacy (2017-Present)
Decoder, Dramaturg (2017-Present)
The Beggar’s Opera: A Multimedia Digital Edition, Project Manager (2017-Present)
Simulating the Wall on YouTube, Project Lead (2018-Present)
Calculating the Politics of Aesthetics: Text-Mining War Movie Reviews on Rotten Tomatoes, PI (2015-2018)</description></item><item><title>Translating</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/translating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/translating/</guid><description>Translations Letter to the Americans, Jean Cocteau, New Directions</description></item><item><title>Writing</title><link>https://hawc2.github.io/writing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hawc2.github.io/writing/</guid><description>PUBLICATIONS EDITORIAL POSITIONS The Programming Historian in English, Assistant Managing Editor (2020-present)
Edited Books Immersive Pedagogy: The DLF Teach Toolkit Volume 2. Principal Editor (2021) William S. Burroughs Cutting Up the Century, Ed. with J. Hawkins, Indiana University Press (2019)
The Travel Agency is on Fire: William S. Burroughs Cuts Up the Canon, Lost &amp;amp; Found: The CUNY Poetics Document Initiative, 5.2 (2015)
The Renaissance of Roland Barthes, Special Issue of The Conversant (with contributions by J.</description></item></channel></rss>